Finding Aid for the Collection of Broadside Ballads from England, Ireland, and the United States LSC.0605
UCLA Library Special Collections
- England
  - Catnach Press (H-I), ca. 1813-1885
    - I'll meet thee at the lane. Happy be thy dreams. Just before the battle, mother. Blamphin, Charles, d. 1895, I'll meet thee at the lane. London, England; W.S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c76; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Indian lass. Oh! If I had some one to rub me. The Indian lass. London, England; Catnach Press (est. 1813). W. S. Fortey, Proprietor, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c77; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Indian lass. Oh! If I had some one to rub me. Oh! If I had some one to rub me. London, England; Catnach Press (est. 1813). W. S. Fortey, Proprietor, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c77; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Insult to the flag of old England. The insult to the flag of old England. London, England; London: Printed by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c78; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Irish navygator. My old wife and I. Clifton, Harry, 1831-1872, My old wife and I. London, England; W.S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c79; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Irish navygator. My old wife and I. Irish navygator. London, England; W.S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c79; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Island of St. Helena. Van Diemans Land. Van Diemans Land. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1838]., Shelfmark: c80; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Island of St. Helena. Van Diemans Land. The Island of St. Helena. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1838]., Shelfmark: c80; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - It is all about the money. It is all about the money. London, England; London: W. S. Fortey, Printer, 2 & 3, monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c81; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - It's naughty but it's nice. Lloyd, Arthur, 1840-1904, It's naughty but it's nice. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam printer and publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c82; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Ivy green. Lovely night. When first I went to sea. Lovely night. London, England; [Ryle] and Co., Printers, 2 and 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, and 35, Hanover street, Portsea, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c83; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Ivy green. Lovely night. When first I went to sea. When first I went to sea. London, England; [Ryle] and Co., Printers, 2 and 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, and 35, Hanover street, Portsea, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c83; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Ivy green. Lovely night. When first I went to sea. Dickens, Charles, 1812-1870, The ivy green. London, England; [Ryle] and Co., Printers, 2 and 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, and 35, Hanover street, Portsea, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c83; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Catnach Press (J-L), ca. 1813-1885
    - Jack Robinson. The banks of Claudy. The banks of Claudy. London, England; Ctnach [sic], 2, Monmouth-Court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c84; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jack Robinson. The banks of Claudy. Hudson, Thomas, Jack Robinson. London, England; Ctnach [sic], 2, Monmouth-Court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c84; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jack Williams the boatswain. Ellen Aureen. A jug of this. A jug of this. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth-Ct. 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c85; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jack Williams the boatswain. Ellen Aureen. A jug of this. Jack Williams the boatswain. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth-Ct. 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c85; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jack Williams the boatswain. Ellen Aureen. A jug of this. Mazzinghi, Joseph, 1765-1844, Ellen Aureen. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth-Ct. 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c85; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Joans ale was new. The lover's meeting. The lovers' meeting. London, England; Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth Court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c86; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Joans ale was new. The lover's meeting. Joans ale was new. London, England; Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth Court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c86; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jockey to the fair. The barrel of pork. Jockey to the fair. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c87; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jockey to the fair. The barrel of pork. The barrel of pork. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c87; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Joe's second dilemma. Joe's second dilemma. London, England; Ryle and Co., Printers, 2 and 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c88; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - John Adwire Anglanna. The suit of green. The suit of green. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c89; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - John Adwire Anglanna. The suit of green. John Adwire Anglanna. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c89; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jolly waggoner. Rambling boys of pleasure. The minute gun at sea. Arnold, Samuel James, 1774-1852, The minute gun at sea. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c90; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jolly waggoner. Rambling boys of pleasure. The minute gun at sea. Rambling boys of pleasure. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c90; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jolly waggoner. Rambling boys of pleasure. The minute gun at sea. Jolly waggoner. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c90; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Judy M'Carty. Norah M'Shane. Judy M'Carty. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c91; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Judy M'Carty. Norah M'Shane. Norah M'Shane. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c91; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Just before the battle, Mother. Enniskillen dragoon. Root, George F. (George Frederick), 1820-1895, Just before the battle, Mother. London, England; W.S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c92; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Just before the battle, Mother. Enniskillen dragoon. Enniskillen dragoon. London, England; W.S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c92; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Just touch the harp gently. Mitchell, Samuel N., 1846-1905, Just touch the harp gently. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c93; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 23 × 8 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kentish cricketer. The bold boatswain of Dover. And overboard he vent. The Kentish cricketer. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c94; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kentish cricketer. The bold boatswain of Dover. And overboard he vent. And overboard he vent. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c94; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kentish cricketer. The bold boatswain of Dover. And overboard he vent. The bold boatswain of Dover. London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c94; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kiss behind the door. Shy, shy, dreadfully shy. Leybourne, George, 1842-1884, The kiss behind the door. London, England; W.S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c95; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kiss behind the door. Shy, shy, dreadfully shy. Leybourne, George, 1842-1884, Shy, shy, dreadfully shy / written & sung by George Leybourne. London, England; W.S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c95; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kiss me Mother, kiss your darling. The bard of Armagh. Lord, Letta C., Kiss me Mother, kiss your darling. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c96; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kiss me Mother, kiss your darling. The bard of Armagh. The bard of Armagh. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c96; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Kitty, the gamekeeper's daughter. Kitty, the gamekeeper's daughter. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c97; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 26 × 10 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Land of old Erin. The star of Glengarry. The Moorish maid. The land of old Erin. London, England; Ryle and Co., Printers, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, and 35, Hanover Street, Portsea, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c98; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Land of old Erin. The star of Glengarry. The Moorish maid. The Moorish maid. London, England; Ryle and Co., Printers, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, and 35, Hanover Street, Portsea, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c98; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Land of old Erin. The star of Glengarry. The Moorish maid. Cook, Eliza, 1818-1889, The star of Glengarry. London, England; Ryle and Co., Printers, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, and 35, Hanover Street, Portsea, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c98; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Lannigan's ball. Lannigan's ball. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam Printer and Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c99; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Lass of Gowrie. The dumb wife. Reid, William, The lass of Gowrie. London, England; Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c100; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Lass of Gowrie. The dumb wife. The dumb wife. London, England; Catnach, Printer, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c100; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Lass of Richmond Hill. The blackbird. Tom Topsail. MacNally, Leonard, 1752-1820, Lass of Richmond Hill. London, England; A. Ryle & Co., Printers 2 and 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c101; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Lass of Richmond Hill. The blackbird. Tom Topsail. Upton, William, fl. 1778, The blackbird. London, England; A. Ryle & Co., Printers 2 and 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c101; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Lass of Richmond Hill. The blackbird. Tom Topsail. Tom Topsail. London, England; A. Ryle & Co., Printers 2 and 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c101; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Liberty and victory for 1874. Liberty and victory for 1874. London, England; W. S. Fortey, Steam Printer, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, W.C., [1874]., Shelfmark: c102; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Life on the ocean wave. I love but thee. Sargent, Epes, 1813-1880, A life on the ocean wave. London, England; A. Ryle & Co., Printers, 2 and 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c103; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Life on the ocean wave. I love but thee. Moore, Thomas, 1779-1852, I love but thee / written by T. Moore, Esq.. London, England; A. Ryle & Co., Printers, 2 and 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c103; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Limerick races. The isle of France. Limerick races. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c104; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Limerick races. The isle of France. The isle of France. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press," by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c104; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Little Mary, the sailor's bride. The primrose girl. Little Mary, the sailor's bride. London, England; Printed by J. Catnach, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials. Sold by Pierce, Southborough, and Bennett, Brighton, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c105; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Little Mary, the sailor's bride. The primrose girl. The primrose girl. London, England; Printed by J. Catnach, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials. Sold by Pierce, Southborough, and Bennett, Brighton, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c105; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Little town's boy. Blow the candle out. The little town's boy. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach," Press by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c106; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Little town's boy. Blow the candle out. Blow the candle out. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach," Press by W. S. Fortey, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c106; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Love not. My Erin, O! Mary, the maid of the green. Mary, the maid of the green. London, England; Ryle & Co., Printers, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, and 35, Hanover Street, Portsea, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c107; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Love not. My Erin, O! Mary, the maid of the green. My Erin, O!. London, England; Ryle & Co., Printers, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, and 35, Hanover Street, Portsea, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c107; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Love not. My Erin, O! Mary, the maid of the green. Love not. London, England; Ryle & Co., Printers, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, and 35, Hanover Street, Portsea, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c107; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Catnach Press (M-N), ca. 1813-1885
    - Man at the Nore. A pound or a penny. The man at the Nore. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam Printer & Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, London, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c108; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Man at the Nore. A pound or a penny. A pound or a penny. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam Printer & Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, London, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c108; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Man on the flying trapeze! Leybourne, George, 1842-1884, The man on the flying trapeze! / written and sung by George Leybourne. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam Printer & Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c109; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 17 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Many happy returns of the day. The village blacksmith. Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth, 1807-1882, The village blacksmith. London, England; London: Printed by W. S. Fortey, 2, & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, London, W.C., [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c110; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Many happy returns of the day. The village blacksmith. Many happy returns of the day. London, England; London: Printed by W. S. Fortey, 2, & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, London, W.C., [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c110; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Maria Louisa['s] lamentation for the green linnet. The rat catcher's daughter. The rat catcher's daughter. London, England; Printed by J. Catnach, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c111; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Maria Louisa['s] lamentation for the green linnet. The rat catcher's daughter. Maria Louisa['s] lamentation for the green linnet. London, England; Printed by J. Catnach, 2, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c111; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 25 × 18 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mary of the moor. The waterman. All's well. The waterman. London, England; Printed by J. Catnach, 2, Monmouth court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c112; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mary of the moor. The waterman. All's well. Dibdin, Thomas, 1771-1841, All's well. London, England; Printed by J. Catnach, 2, Monmouth court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c112; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mary of the moor. The waterman. All's well. Turner, J. W. (Joseph W.), Mary of the moor. London, England; Printed by J. Catnach, 2, Monmouth court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1835]., Shelfmark: c112; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mind your own business. Mind your own business. London, England; Ryle and Co., Printers, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c113; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 3 ill. (wood engravings); 26 × 18 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Minnie. Minnie. London, England; Ryle and Co., Printers, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1845 and 1858]., Shelfmark: c114; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 15 × 8 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mitchell's address. Nelly Gray. Mitchell's address. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press" by W. S. Fortey (late A. Ryle) 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c115; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mitchell's address. Nelly Gray. Hanby, Benjamin Russel, 1833-1867, Nelly Gray. London, England; London: Printed at the "Catnach Press" by W. S. Fortey (late A. Ryle) 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Bloomsbury, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c115; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 1 ill. (wood engraving); 25 × 20 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mollie darling. Belle Mahone. Hays, Will. S. (William Shakespeare), 1837-1907, Mollie darling. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam Printer & Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c116; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 24 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mollie darling. Belle Mahone. McNaughton, John Hugh, 1829-1891, Belle Mahone. London, England; W. S. Fortey, General Steam Printer & Publisher, 2 & 3, Monmouth Court, Seven Dials, [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c116; 1 sheet ([1] p.): 2 ill. (wood engravings); 24 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Most laughable and curious dialogue which took place between a married couple in this town. A most laughable and curious dialogue which took place between a married couple in this town.... London, England; J. Catnach, Printer, 2, & 3, Monmouth-court, 7 Dials, [between 1813 and 1838]., Shelfmark: c117; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 25 × 19 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mother would comfort me. By kind to thy father. Toast and sentiments. Martha the milkman's daughter. Martha the milkman's daughter. London, England; W. S. Fortey, Printer, Monmouth Ct., London. W.C., [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c118; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 20 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mother would comfort me. By kind to thy father. Toast and sentiments. Martha the milkman's daughter. Sawyer, Charles C. (Charles Carroll), b. 1833, Mother would comfort me. London, England; W. S. Fortey, Printer, Monmouth Ct., London. W.C., [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c118; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 20 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Mother would comfort me. By kind to thy father. Toast and sentiments. Martha the milkman's daughter. Woodbury, I. B. (Isaac Baker), 1818-1858, Be kind to thy father. London, England; W. S. Fortey, Printer, Monmouth Ct., London. W.C., [between 1858 and 1885]., Shelfmark: c118; 1 sheet ([1] p.); 24 × 20 cm. (Box 7, Folder 6)